Finding aid for the Henry Clay Frick Papers, Series II: Correspondence, 1882-1929, undated HCFF.1.2
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Whitney, Belle - Whitridge (Box 94, Folder 3)
  Whitney, J.E., 1908
  Whitney, Livingston, 1902
  Whitney, Mary L., 1898
  Whitney, W.C., 1899-1904
  Whitridge, F.W., 1914
  Whitridge, Lucy (Mrs. F.W. Whitridge), 1917
  Whitridge, Madeleine Gary (Mrs. Andrew H. Witridge), 1916
- Whitson - Wick (Box 94, Folder 4)
  Whitson, G.S., 1906
  Whitson, J.T., 1914
  Whitty, J.H., 1914
  Who's Who(London, England), 1919
  Whyel, Harry, 1899-1901
  Wick, George D., 1901-1902
  Wick, Henry, 1896-1905
  Wick, Myron C., 1901, 1904
- Wickersham - Willard (Box 94, Folder 5)
  Wickersham, George, 1908-1912
  Wicks, Ron F., 1906
  Widener, George D., 1906
  Widener, Joseph E., 1912-1919
  Widener, P.A.B., 1910
  Wieder, Leon, 1922
  Wiggin, Albert H., 1912
  Wight, C.S., 1897, no year
  Wild, Lucy E., 1903
  Wildman, Edwin, 1916
  Wilell[?], W. Wildey, 1900
  Wiley, John A., 1891
  Wilhelm, John, Jr., 1901
  Wilhelm, N.O., 1916
  Wilkey[?], John, 1889
  Wilkins, Beriah, 1901
  Wilkins, W.E., 1916
  Wilkins, Warren C., 1916
  Wilkinsburg Bank (Wilkinsburg, Pa.), 1899-1900
  Willard, Daniel, 1910-1916
  Willard, De Forest, 1909
  Willard, H.P., 1903[?]
- Willaume - Wilmerding (Box 94, Folder 6)
  Willaume, E., 1906
  Willets, Gilson, 1906
  William D. Kerfott and Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1909
  William Lewis and Sons (London, England), 1899
  William Morris Imbrie and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Wm. Riker and Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1905
  Williams, A.H., 1903
  Williams and Morris (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1887
  Williams, Arthur, 1912
  Williams, B.W., 1907
  Williams, Clark, 1908
  Williams, David, 1896
  Williams, David E., 1886
  Williams, E.F., 1915
  Williams, E.P., 1906
  Williams, Edgar, 1904
  Williams, H., 1906
  Williams, H.D., 1916
  Williams, J.H., 1912
  Williams, J.W., 1900
  Williams, Oliver, 1900
  Williams, R.H., 1905
  Williams, Thos. H., 1901
  Williamson, F.E., 1908
  Willick, Lucinda F., 1902, 1907
  Willis, E.J., 1903
  Willis, Louis, 1903
  Willock, James H., 1892
  Willoughby, Charles H., 1914
  Willson, Geo. V., 1902
  Wilmerding, Lily Fay (Mrs. C.H. Wilmerding), 1912
- Wilsey - Wilson, J.F. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  Wilsey, Frank D., 1915
  Wilson, A.G., 1900-1912
  Wilson, Anna C., 1906
  Wilson, Charles H., 1915
  Wilson, Dallett H., 1906
  Wilson, E.B., 1898
  Wilson, Erasmus, 1915
  Wilson Farm [no place], 1909
  Wilson G.S., 1890
  Wilson, G.W., 1894-1911
  Wilson, George H., 1899, 1904
  Wilson, Georgia O., 1900
  Wilson, H.B., 1908
  Wilson, Harry, 1913
  Wilson, Howard S., 1909
  Wilson, J.B., 1915-1916
  Wilson, J.F., 1906
- Wilson, John S., 1885-1906 (Box 94, Folder 8-9)
- Wilson, Lawrence - Winter, Henry (Box 94, Folder 10)
  Wilson, Lawrence W., 1902
  Wilson, M.F., 1904
  Wilson, R.A., 1903
  Wilson, W.B., 1919
  Wilson, W.T., 1902
  Wilson, Woodrow, 1917
  Windsor Trust Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Wingfield, George, 1909-1914
  Winslow, George Scott, 1906
  Winslow, William C., 1901
  Winsor, Robert, 1909, 1912
  Winter, Henry B., 1897-1898
- Winter, W.W. - Wise, Charles Henry (Box 94, Folder 11)
  Winter, W.W., 1914
  Winthrop, Henry Rogers, 1905-1919
  Winthrop Normal and Industrial College [no place], no year
  Wiston, Effie Ellsler, 1906
  Wirsing, J.J., 1890
  Wisby, Johannes Hrolf, 1900
  Wise, Charles Henry, 1911
- Wise, Jesse H., 1909-1915 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Wise, John - Wood, Katharine (Box 95, Folder 2)
  Wise, John S., 1903
  Wise, R.M., 1899
  Witt, Robert C., 1912
  Wittenberg College [no place], 1913
  Wm. A. White and Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1921
  Wm. C. Ahl Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906
  Wohltman, J.J., 1900
  Wolf, F.L., 1891
  Wolfersburger, P.S., 1887
  Wolff, B., Jr., 1886, 1889
  Woman's Christian Temperance Union [no place], 1907
  The Woman's Club (Homestead, Pa.), 1906
  Woman's Press Club (New York, N.Y.), 1915-1916
  Women's Apparel Association of Women's Oversea Hospitals (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1918
  Wood, E.M., 1901
  Wood, Georgette, 1915
  Wood, Isaac L., 1912-1915
  Wood, J.M., 1901
  Wood, Joseph, 1890-1917
  Wood, Katharine W., 1912
- Wood, Leonard - Woods, Cyrus (Box 95, Folder 3)
  Wood, Leonard, 1917, 1919
  Wood, W.L., 1911
  Wood, W.S., 1886-1887
  Wood, William M., 1903-1906
  Wood, William S., 1906
  Woodberry, S., 1907
  Woodburn, B.F., Mrs., 1896
  Woodburn, M.A., 1897-1901
  Woodbury Electric Co. (Beverly, Mass.), 1903
  Woodbury, John P., 1907-1908
  Woodcock, W.H., 1902
  Woodhull, J., 1897
  Woodruff, Timothy L., 1908, 1911
  Woods, Arthur, 1916
  Woods, C.W., 1912
  Woods, Cyrus E., 1906-1919
- Woods, Edward - Woollard (Box 95, Folder 4)
  Woods, Edward A., 1899-1918
  Woods, Lawrence C., 1912-1920
  Woods, W.L., 1898-1903
  Woods, William S., 1906
  Woods, Wm. H., 1911
  Woodside, Nevin, 1896
  Woodside, Robert, 1905
  Woodward, George, 1906
  Woodward, James O., 1909
  Woodwell, Joseph R., 1908, 1911
  Wooldridge, C.L., 1916
  Woollard, William E., 1911
- Woolley - Wooten (Box 95, Folder 5)
  Woolley, George H., 1906
  Woolley, Jabez, 1909-1915
  Wooster City Schools (Wooster, Ohio), 1913
  Wooster Voice(Wooster, Ohio), 1900
  Wooten Desk Co. (Richmond, Ind.), 1888
- Workingmans - Wyre (Box 95, Folder 6)
  Workingmans Savings Bank (Allegheny, Pa.), 1896
  World(New York, N.Y.), 1905, undated
  Wortley, R.M. Stuart, 1916
  Wortmann, Edw., 1914
  Wouters, Frank, 1917-1919
  Wray, F. Aslett, 1914
  Wright, F.C., 1916
  Wright, J. Merrill, 1904
  Wright, J.O., 1906, 1914
  Wright, J. Robert, 1906
  Wright, James M., 1910, 1913
  Wright, Samuel J., 1912
  Wright, Theodore, 1907
  Wright, Thruston, 1913
  Wright, W.F., 1897
  Wright, Wm., 1899
  Wurster, C. William, 1900
  Wyatt and Trowt (Pride's Crossing, Mass.), 1909
  Wyckoff, Spencer Cone, 1908
  Wyer, Raymond, 1915
  Wykes, Hunter, 1917
  Wyman, Walter C., 1919
  Wymard, J.K., 1898
  Wynne, Peter, 1917
  Wyre, Leila A., 1916
- Wyness, George, 1905-1920 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Xavier - Young Men's Christian Association (Box 95, Folder 8)
  Xavier, Sister Mary, 1894-1910
  Xavierian Brothers (Danvers, Mass.), 1909
  Yager, J.C., 1908
  Yahn, S.G., 1898
  Yale University Press, Chronicles of America Agency (New York, N.Y.), 1919
  Yates, Frederick J., 1912
  Yates Realty Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908
  Yoakum, B.F., 1902, 1904
  Youghiogheny Bank (Connellsville, Pa.), 1886
  Young, Alton M., 1913, 1918
  Young, E.P., 1907
  Young, George W., 1909-1910
  Young, Jacob, 1897
  Young, James C., 1904
  Young, James R., 1900
  Young Men's Christian Association [various locations], 1890-1910
- Young, S. Cameron - Youngstown (Box 95, Folder 9)
  Young, S. Cameron, 1903, 1905
  Young, S. Edward, 1901-1903
  Young Women's and Young Men's Christian Association [no place], 1913
  Youngstown Iron Sheet and Tube Co. (Youngstown, Ohio), 1901-1904
- Zachariah - Zug (Box 95, Folder 10)
  Zachariah, William, Jr., 1906
  Zahniser, J.J., 1919
  Zelch, Walter A., 1905
  Zellner, O.C., 1912, 1919
  Ziegler, J.C., 1909
  Zeigler, William, Jr., 1913
  Zimmerman, John L., 1913
  Zimmerman, Samuel G., 1909
  Zinn, George A., 1912-1913
  Zion Evangelical Church (Wooster, Ohio), 1912
  Zuck, J.R., 1913
  Zug, George B., 1904